Guide to the Rice News photo files, 1995-2006 UA 357
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series I: 1995-1999, 206899
  - Subseries C: 1997, 206957
    - September 11, 1997, 206980 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Photographs and negatives include: Nathan Smalley, Peter Shaddock, Madeleine Albright, Lee Hoage-Jamail, Yasir Arafat, Janet Reno, Jack Kemp, Edward Djerejian, Jenny Ferng, Michelle Engleman, Louren Reed, Paula Wynn, Yayoi Kusama, Rice University Art Gallery, Chandler Davidson, Monica Bacallao, Ellsworth Milburn, and Hai Chen.
    - September 18, 1997, 206981 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      Photographs and negatives include: Rice vs. Air Force football game, Rice football, "Operation Sellout" game, Arturo Montes, Henry Rosovsky, Sherry Hughes, Destiny Suarez, Lance Berkman, Joseph Cathey, Kevin Joseph, Marching Owl Band (MOB), Heather Michelle-Stewart, Sol Bodner, Charles Koontz, Scott Rennie, Malcolm Gillis, and Certificate of Enshrinement award winners.
    - September 25, 1997, 206982 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Photographs and negatives include: Karen Kossie, Christoph Eschenbach, and the Shepherd School Symphony Orchestra.
    - October 2, 1997, 206983 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Photographs and negatives include: Larry McMurtry, Margaret Fox, Kylie Spence, Carol Quillen, and Sean Harris.
    - October 9, 1997, 206984 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Photographs and negatives include: Dennis Hendrix, Saint Arnold Brewing Company, Kevin Bartol, Brock Wagner, Emil Fernandez, Jesse Torres, Tim Case, Jeff Humphreys, Bryan Cook, Demetrios Demopolous, Jean Ashmore, David Remnick, Pol D. Spanos, Farley Tobin, Baker Institute, and Fausto Vazquez.
    - October 16, 1997, 206985 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      Photographs and negatives include: Cynthia Wunder, Eric Zapata, and Bina Agarwal.
    - October 23, 1997, 206986 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      Photographs and negatives include: Michael R. Beschloss, James A. Baker III, Baker Hall dedication ceremony, E. William Barnett, Malcolm Gillis, Henry Kissinger, Kay Bailey Hutchinson, Bob Lanier, Mikhail Gorbachev, Edward Djerejian, Kenneth Lay, Bernard Shaw, and Warren Christopher.
    - October 30, 1997, 206987 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      Photographs and negatives include: Paul Moore, Rebecca Searl, "You're a Good Man, Charlie Brown" production, Elnoretha Adams, Malcolm Gillis, Elizabeth George, Stephanie Fuller, Harold Hyman, Edith Orlin, Thomas Estle, and Mark Williamson.
    - November 6, 1997, 206988 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      Photographs and negatives include: Rice Homecoming, Daryl Shorter, David Medina, Gabriel Medina, and Ken Hatfield.
    - November 13, 1997, 206989 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      Photographs and negatives include: Rice Homecoming, James Kinsey, Donell Victorian, Youth Advocates Inc., Wiess College, and Mike Gustin.
    - November 20, 1997, 206990 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      Photographs and negatives include: Jim Rahe, David Ikenberry, Charles Howard "To the absent friend" exhibit at the Rice University Art Gallery, Lee P. Brown, Rob Mosbacher Jr., AirLifeLine, Jamie Hanks, Michael Hanks, and Alan Grob.
    - December 4, 1997, 206991 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      Photographs and negatives include: Jonel Curl, Mary Lou Margave, Vonqueta Hicks, the Graduate Student Loan Closet, Faculty Women's Club project, Tony Gorry, Gale Stokes, James A. Baker III, Edward Djerejian, Nursultan Nazarbaev, the Society of Rice University Women, and the Rice Land Lumber Company.
    - December 11, 1997, 206992 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      Photographs and negatives include: Lisa McCormick, Jack Mitchell, Charles Duncan, Malcolm Gillis, Anne Duncan, Marcia J. Citron, Rice School of Architecture project by Chad Machen, Brian Burke, Andrew Albers, Alane Truitt, and Brett Zamore.
  - Subseries D: 1998, 206993
    - January 15, 1998, 206994 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      Photographs and negatives include: Dominique de Menil, Gerald A. Cohen, and W.O. King.
    - January 22, 1998, 206995 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      Photographs and negatives include: Ellen Butler, Francisca Castillo, Carlos Fighetti, Kim Neuscheler, Kathy Dy, Project Row, Danny Samuels, Nonya Grenader, Robert Fleming, Pat Kambhu, Roger Reuter, Eugen Radulescu, Neill Binford, Rice Women's Basketball, Rice Men's Basketball, Jarvis Kelley Sanni, and Jenny Cafferty.
    - January 29, 1998, 206996 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      Photographs and negatives include: Harry Wu, the Black Student Association, Martin Luther King Jr. vigil, Harith Paki Nelson, Jaime Middleton, Rev. Frank L. Chatmon, "Dona Provi's Garden" by Antonio Martorell in the Rice University Art Gallery, Niko Severson, Lisa McCormick, Norman Fischer, LaNelle McReynolds, Mahmoud A. El-Gamal, and Chandler Davidson.
    - February 15, 1998, 206997 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      Photographs and negatives include: Arlo Guthrie, Tony Elam, David Sedmak, Go-Texan Champion Chili Cook-off, Bob Jaster, Tracey Rhoades, Victor Kato, and the Houston Pan-Cultural Film Festival.
    - February 19, 1998, 206998 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      Photographs and negatives include: Bringfriede Kahrs, Malcolm Gillis, Bremen school discussion, Marc Robert, Nichel Heinijer, Pierre-Alain Jaussi, Francoise Ducret, Jean-Claude Walther, Larry Rachleff, Rice Owls Baseball, Jeremy Bates, Christof Spieler, Shepherd School orchestra, David Medina, and Tom Hiles.
    - February 12, 1998, 206999 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      Photographs and negatives include: Lunar New Year Festival, Chinese Student Association, Korean Student Association, Taiwanese Student Association, South Asian Society, Vietnamese Student Association, Becky Frederickson, Alicia Schade, Malcolm Gillis, Hunter Rowe, Richard Wolin, Josuzette Reed, Danny Samuels, Tommy Brasher, Ahmed Maher El Sayed, and Dore Gold.
    - February 26, 1998, 207000 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      Photographs and negatives include: Ramona Hicks, Women's Resource Center anniversary, A. J. Jamal, IMPACT award winners, FotoFest, "Keep on Rolling" at Rice Media Center by Jesse Demartino, Erwin Teufel, Malcolm Gillis, James A. Baker III, Jane Chance, Lucille Fultz, Deborah Harter, Carol Quillen, Jinny Sisson, Penelope Bennett, Lisa Bryan, Jackie Ehlers, Cynthia Lanius, Karen George, Erin Devitt, Joy Roth, Claire Carman, Carrell Covington, Liana Gefter, Melissa Jacobs, Stephanie Taylor, Ravi Sohal, Jane Trinh, and Catherine Clack.
    - March 12, 1998, 207001 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Photographs, slides and negatives include: Peter Nordlander, Moshe Vardi, Robert Fowler, Paul Brace, Andrew Barron, Houston Fire Department, George Phillips, Frank Shipman, Ric Stoll, Dana Durbin, Blanton Lewis, Jordan Konisky, Tony Elam, and Charles Richard.
    - March 19, 1998, 207002 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Photographs and negatives include: Dean Shank, Volodyia piano and signatures, Wayne Graham, disc golf, Richard Smalley, Wang Meng, Steve Lewis, John Horner, and Brian Gibson.
    - March 26, 1998, 207003 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      Photographs and negatives include: Beer Bike, new Beer Bike track, Baker 13, Norma Jean Autry, Laura Huckabay, Kimathy Blackwood, Alexander Lebed, Sherry Bennett, Simon Clark, Tanya Dunlap, Rebecca Sherman, Stephanie Taylor, Stuart Douglas, Edward Said, Hakeem Olajuwon, Robert Curl, David Lancaster, Frank Tittel, and Dirk Richter.
    - April 2, 1998, 207004 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      Photographs and negatives include: Jennifer Brown, Michele Wen Tang, Lee Brown, Edward Said, and the Rice Scholar-Athlete Banquet.
    - April 9, 1998, 207005 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      Photographs and negatives include: the Business Info Center, Vicki Calvin, Geoff Love, Jones School, Stuart Eizenstat, William E. Leuchtenburg, KTRU Outdoor Show, the Phil Gayle Trio, electric bus, Nell Noddings, and Jennifer Perez.
    - April 16, 1998, 207006 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      Photographs and negatives include: Will Robedee, the George R. Brown Forensics team, Darshan Amrit, Jason Wehling, Joshua Roberts, Rice University Art Galley exhibit "COLLAPSE: The Commodification of Talent," Habitat for Humanity, and Lillian Ortiz.
    - April 23, 1998, 207007 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      Photographs and negatives include: Dennis Banks, Mallcolm Gillis, Robert Schwartz, Marcie Doughty, Eileen Grant, Consuelo Sanchez, Gracie Henry, Margaret Cortez, Albert Jackson, Muhammed Al-Shaali, Edward Djerejian, Clovis Maksoud, and the Summer Sports Camp.
    - April 30, 1998, 207008 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      Photographs and negatives include: Richard Tapia, GirlTECH workshop, Patricia Martin, Rowland Smith Jr., Adan Herrera, Paul Manwell, David Hindman, Daniel King, Jill Daugherty, and Kevin Conrad.
    - May 7, 1998, 207009 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      Photographs and negatives include: Bob Stein, Terrence Doody, Charles Stewart, John Hutchinson, John Olson, and Eugenia Georges.
    - May 28, 1998, 207010 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      Photographs and negatives include: Robin Sickles, Gus A. Schill Jr., Malcolm Gillis, IBM Corporation, Kurt Vonnegut, Thomas Scott Brown, Alexis Bacon, Shana Stern Warren, students in the Italian Club and French Club, Terry Cloudman, Russell Price, Roland Smith Jr., George H. W. Bush, Barbara Bush, Rice graduation, Jones College magisters.
    - June 25, 1998, 207011 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      Photographs and negatives include: the Association of Rice Alumni, Jimmy Carter Work Project, Sheila Fletcher, the Department of Facilities and Engineering sand castle competition, Sam Venneri, NASA Collaboration, Malcolm Gillis, Richard Smalley, Nick Lampson, Ken Bentsen, Sidney Burrus, Richard Tapia, Israel Galvan, Joe Arnold, George Strait, Ayisha McMillan, Jimmy Carter, Rosalyn Carter, Varick Stringham Jr., Lea Rabin, and Edward Djerejian.
    - July 30, 1998, 207012 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      Photographs and negatives include: Sai Paranjpye, David Auston, B.N. Murali, David Medina, Richard Torres, Arturo DeLeon, Yvonne Hernandez, Anandi Sheth, and Urban Immersion.
    - August 27, 1998, 207013 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      Photographs and negatives include: Lovett College, Orientation Week (O-Week), Operation Sellout Part II, Rice Owls Football, Malcolm Gillis, Ken Hatfield, Bobby May, John Polick, Kathryn Costello, Tony Elam, Ryulchi Kuki, Ken Kennedy, Moshe Vardi, Michael Carroll, Marek Kimmell, and Larry McMurtry.
    - September 3, 1998, 207014 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      Photographs and negatives include: Hakeem Olajuwan, Charles Torello, Sue Hutchings, Matt Fraser, Stephen Keene exhibit in the Rice University Art Gallery, Alice Hill, Mitch Ackel, Rice Dance Theatre, Kimberlee Benn, Katy Busworth, and Kristina Raniere.
    - September 10, 1998, 207015 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      Photographs and negatives include: Scott Wise, Kent Anderson, Dean Currie, Malcolm Gillis, Amaud Chevalier, Stewart Morris, Charles Szalkowski, Jesse Turner, Vianna Davila, Saramae Nilsson, Barbara Kile, Viola Benavidez, Ryan Hall, Iris Hurtado, Todd LeBlanc, Bradford Strom, Jessica Watkins, and William Deigaard.
    - September 17, 1998, 207016 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      Photographs and negatives include: Eugen Radulescu, Bob Cesario, Jamail Plaza construction, and Jane Callan.
    - September 24, 1998, 207017 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - October 1, 1998, 207018 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - October 8, 1998, 207019 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - October 15, 1998, 207020 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - October 22, 1998, 207021 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - October 29, 1998, 207022 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - November 5, 1998, 207023 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      Photographs and negatives include: Malcolm Gillis, Richard Smalley, Jaron Lanier, Nicole Eisenman's "Behavior" installation at the Rice University Art Gallery, Teach for America Week, Fondren library, Jeanine White, and Robert Dix.
    - November 12, 1998, 207024 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      Photographs and negatives include: Tom Broussard, David A. Mittelstadt, Barry Smith, Harold Hyman, Jane Dailey, Michael Willrich, and Kerry Keck.
    - Nobember 19, 1998, 207025 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      Photographs and negatives include: Alex Hernandez, Rice Honduras Relief Effort, Jason Skaer, and the National Association for Computing MAchinery South Central USA Programming Competition.
    - December 3, 1998, 207026 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      Photographs and negatives include: "16 Houses: Owning a House in the City," Michael Bell, Mardie Oakes, Stacy Ware, and the Wild Art series.
    - December 10, 1998, 207027 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      Photographs and negatives include: Bob Truscott, Old Chemistry Building Renovation, Paul Sanders, Lisa Chang, Jeffrey Clarke, Michelle Dass Pickard, Susan Lieberman, Daniel Ma, Dennis Lu, Mrudula Penta, Dan West, Brooke Ames, Tumi Johnson, Mondro Barmam, Coffeehouse, and Frank Bearden.
  - Subseries E: 1999, 207028
    - January 14, 1999, 207029 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      Photographs and negatives include: E. William Barnett, Judith Brown, Malcolm Gillis, D. Kent Anderson, Bobby Azamian, Justyna Gudzowska, and Kyle Cavanaugh.
    - January 21, 1999, 207030 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      Photographs and negatives include: Deron Neblett, Patricia Martin, Jen Cooper, Karin Pearl, Rex McLellan, Rhonda Callendar, Brian Mayeaux, Enrique Barrera, Candi Hudson, Adam Andrea, Gary Cisneros, Justin Kerr, Eric Christiansen, Jay Laughman, Nancy Espinoza, Jessie Hawkins, Rice groundskeepers, and Susan Lurie.
    - January 28, 1999, 207031 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      Photographs and negatives include: the Martin Luther King Jr. candlelight vigil, James A. Baker III, Edward Djerejian, Bernice King, Shaun Scott, Edward Cox, Zenaido Comacho, "The History of the World" Rice University Art Gallery installation by Michael Petry, Michael Petry, Stephen Klineberg, Carroll Robinson, Malcolm Gillis, the Black Student Association, William Shakespeare's First Folio at Woodson Research Center, Melodious Voices of Praise, and Melanie R. Stagger.
    - February 4, 1999, 207032 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      Photographs and negatives include: Karen Yaworski, Amar Pai, James Mischka, Richard Avant of Deloitte and Touche Consulting Group, E. William Barnett, Jack Blanton, Alex Hernandez, the Rice Honduras Relief Effort, Morela Hernandez, and Malcolm Gillis.
    - February 11, 1999, 207033 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      Photographs and negatives include: Jurgen Timm, Malcolm Gillis, Fritz Schaumann, Douglas Mitchell, Edward Albee, Rob Bundy, Yo-Yo Ma, Zenaido Camacho, Allison Winnike, Marion Hicks, and Elsa Arguello.
    - February 18, 1999, 207034 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      Photographs and negatives include: Malcolm Gillis, Bernadette J. Brooten, Benjamin Alire Saenz, Kelechi Anderson, Victor Lopez, "What the Butler Saw," Mike Simon, Maria Collins, and Marla Brumfield.
    - February 25, 1999, 207035 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      Photographs and negatives include: Roger "Trey" Wright, Mark Escott, Space Science renovations, Robin Feng, Lunar New Year festival, Steven Pinker, Women's Resource Center third anniversary, Rice Emergency Medical Services (REMS), Christine Borgstrom, Stephen Chao, Alex Flores, Monica Ramos, Clay Juckett, John Cloudman, Noah Reiter, Laura Grable, Mark Escott, Sean Joyce, Tim Miller, Andi Tenner, Clayton Hall, Sandheep Surendran, Danny Chelius, and Ginger Mills.
    - March 4, 1999, 207036 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      Photographs and negatives include: Yo-Yo Ma.
    - March 18, 1999, 207037 (Box 9, Folder 14)
      Photographs and negatives include: Lars Lerup, Sohela Farokhi, "A Workshop for Librarians and Archivists," Phyllis Martin, Melinda Flannery, Richard Tapia, Shirley Malcolm, Caroline Caskey, Christine Mei Chow, Michael Chow, Doug Foshee, Zenaido Camacho, Keith Anderson, and Janet Lowe.
    - March 25, 1999, 207038 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      Photographs and negatives include: "Time Not Wasted" exhibition by Jane Miller in the Rice University Art Gallery, Christopher Johnson, Katherine Solon, Elizabeth Gabriel, John Germany, Jesse. H. Jones Graduate School of Management students, and James McPherson.
    - April 1, 1999, 207039 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Photographs and negatives include: Beer Bike, Steven Klineberg, Albert Pope, Stephen Fox, Gloria Ladson-Billings, Phil Gramm, Malcolm Gillis, arboretum grand opening, Andre Watts, Jones Beer Bike team, and Michael Hammond.
    - April 8, 1999, 207040 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Photographs and negatives include: Julia Robinson, Heather Hawley, Matt Frost, David Gergen, James A. Baker III, Edward Djerejian, Lani Guinier, Jim Wooten, Keith Meehan Bill Wilson, David Minter, David Nirenberg, and Pam Walker.
    - April 15, 1999, 207041 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      Photographs and negatives include: Rice University Native American Student Association Powow, Rice Community Garden, Amanda Barnum, Staff Advisory Committee, Jennifer Overton, Jet Prendeville, Mary Margaret Williamson, Teresa Parks, Bill Lassiter, Michael Winters, Pat Kambhu, Somarine Diep, Kyle Cavanaugh, Jana Callan, Scott Brasher, Heather Dodge, Alvin R. Tarlov, James A. Baker III, Bob Lanier, Bob Stein, Edward Djerejian, and William P. Hobby Jr.
    - April 22, 1999, 207042 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      Photographs and negatives include: George Strait, Eric Johnson, Terry Shepard, Lani Guinier, Gale Stokes, Edward Djerejian, Fran Moshiri, Daria Lawrence, Steve Currall, Paula Sanders, Bob Dipboye, Maureen Craig, Sarah Betz, Sarah Rodgerson, and Ben Serebrin.
    - April 29, 1999, 207043 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      Photographs and negatives include: Garry Eudey, Lachlan McArthur, Jon Warren, and Nancy Rowe.
    - May 6, 1999, 207044 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      Photographs and negatives include: Damon Thames, Rice Owls baseball, Thomas Friedman, Edith Wyschogrod, and Jason Wehling.
    - May 13, 1999, 207045 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      Photographs and negatives include: Bob Patten, Mikki Hebl, the Bayou City Road Runners, Zhiyong Gao, Steve J. Cox, Chandler Davidson, Yildiz Bayazitoglu, Deborah Harter, and Edward L. Cox.
    - May 27, 1999, 207046 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      Photographs and negatives include: Commencement, Patrick Thomas, Rosemary Yiameos, Theodore Howard, Liz Brown, Matthew Chrisman, Amy Bender, James Henderson, Ryan McMullan, Gilbert M. Grosvenor, James A. Baker III, Malcolm Gillis, Bob Dalton, Terry Koonce, Albert Kidd, Al Hirshberg, Helmut Schmidt, Thomas Friedman, and Edward Djerejian.
    - June 24, 1999, 207047 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      Photographs and negatives include: Special Olympics Summer Games, summer construction, the Basmati Quartet, Fia Mancini, David Filner, Alessandra Jennings, Erin Breene, Zenaido Camacho, Paul Sutera, Dana Hoyland, Marguerite Guinn, Bonnie Brelsford, Phil Gramm, Carole Keeton Rylander, Dean Currie, William Deigaard, and the Donne Di Domani Awards.
    - July 29, 1999, 207048 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      Photographs and negatives include: Rice Rowing Club, Hannes Hoger, Cathryn Fine, Bastille Day, the Woodson Research Center, Lee Pecht, Reckling Park, Joe Broussard, Nora Quiocho, and Robert Patten.
    - August 26, 1999, 207049 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      Photographs and negatives include: the Carbon Nanotechnology Laboratory, Bernard Harris, Robert Eckels, Malcolm Gillis, Gene Hackerman, Norman Hackerman, Richard Smalley, Nick Lampson, Ken Bentsen, Henry Hernandez, Blanca Garza, Alberto R. Gonzales, Andrew MacKay, Gwen Thomas, Gunes Ercal, KTRU, Patty Base, and Rice matriculation.
    - September 2, 1999, 207050 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      Photographs and negatives include: O-Week, Kazahra Gallegos, LeMeichia Burries, Chris Sims, Martha Borrowman, Wallace Dominey, and Judd Smith.
    - September 9, 1999, 207051 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      Photographs, slides, and negatives include: Chris Kilgore, Kristen Griffen, and Cristy Moreno.
    - September 16, 1999, 207052 (Box 10, Folder 14)
      Photographs and negatives include: Rusty Holleman, Emma Phillips, John Chao, Anne Countiss, "Hoss" installation at the Rice University Art Gallery by Barry McGee, Kyle Henry, and J. D. Allshouse.
    - September 23, 1999, 207053 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      Photographs and negatives include: Bill Taylor, Les Hulsey, Arnaud Chevalier, Julia Smith Wellner, Dean Currie, Rice Graduate Apartments, and D. Kent Anderson.
    - September 30, 1999, 207054 (Box 10, Folder 16)
      Photographs and negatives include: Evan Pankey, Megan Francis, Jeffrey Blackinton, Petra Pilgrim, Deepthy Kishore, Alisa Tijerina, Liora Danan, Cynthia Guadalupe, Rebecca Mackiernan, Malcolm Gillis, Phil Gramm, Kay Bailey Huchison, Ken Hatfield, Hanna Gray, Mikki Hebl, and the Hewlett Seminars.
    - October 7, 1999, 207055 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Photographs and negatives include: the Gotham Quartet, Lun Jiang, Sheila Browne, Cheng-Hou Lee, Quan Jian, the Anderson Quartet, Jeffrey Boga, Marianne Henry, Michael Cameron, Diedra Lawrence, Michael Bloomberg, Geoffrey Potts, Alex Knapp, Envision grant cooking classes, Tony Ro, James Pomerantz, Randi Martin, Sydney Lamb, and Jim Tour.
    - October 14, 1999, 207056 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Photographs and negatives include: Erin Engelhardt, Ilana Bromberg, Pete Irot, John Bennett, Malcolm Gillis, new Wiess College groundbreaking, E. William Barnett, John Hutchinson, Paula Hutchinson, Emma Hutchinson, and Peter E. Veruki.
    - October 21, 1999, 207057 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      Photographs and negatives include: Aliaquanda Derrick, Robert Arellano, Olivia Liang, Barber Day, Mary Voswinkel, the Graduate Student Association, Scott Sitton, Julia Smith Wellner, Andrea Frolic, Kristin Griffith, Ashley Lowe, and Devra Jaffe.
    - October 28, 1999, 207058 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      Photographs and negatives include: Isaac Stern, Sidney Burrus, Ann Hightower, Gilbert R. Whitaker, Vince Hennessy, Rice lemonade stand, Emerson Hankamer, Chad Smith, John B. Herrington, Carl Buck, Michael Capellas, and Andres Pastrana Arango.
    - November 4, 1999, 207059 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      Photographs and negatives include: Project Pumpkin, Rice Student Volunteer Program, Thomas B. Fargo, Mary McIntire, Nawal El-Saadawi, and Nelson Mandela.
    - November 11, 1999, 207060 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      Photographs and negatives include: Isaac Stern, Brett Zamore, Fifth Ward remodeling, Todd Welbes, Amy Boratko, and the Rice Players production of "Post-mortem."
    - November 18, 1999, 207061 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      Photographs and negatives include: the Houston Area Urban League, Malcolm Gillis, Sylvia Brooks, Ann Wright, Jan West, Douglas Simmons, and Stephen Zeff.
    - December 2, 1999, 207062 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      Photographs and negatives include: Ellsworth Millburn, Moira Gunn, Sammy the Owl, and Carl MacDowell.
    - December 9, 1999, 207063 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      Photographs and negatives include: Kathleen DeSilva, Zenaido Camacho, the Holiday Bazaar, Kara Liggett, Kirra Jordan, Alex Bougaieff, C.M. "Hank" Hudspeth, Demaris Hudspeth, Malcolm Gillis, Daryl Williams, Kathleen Matthews, and Gus Scuseria. This folder also includes a copy of "Shaping a Century: Rice Contributes to Evolution of Houston, the World," including essays by Malcolm Gillis, John Boles, and Rice Deans.
    - 1999-2000, 207064 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Series II: 2000-2006, 207065
  - Subseries A: 2000, 207066
    - January 13, 2000, 207067 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      Photographs and negatives include: Virginia Stanfield, and the "Inertial Field" exhibition at Rice University Art Gallery by Stephen Hendee.
    - January 20, 2000, 207068 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      Photographs and negatives include: Larry Alemany, Helena Michie, the Heritage Society museum, School of Architecture's Rice Building Workshop, Martin Luther King Jr. candlelight vigil, Malcolm Gillis, Vanessa Gilmore, the Black Student Association, and the Majestic Voices of Praise.
    - January 27, 2000, 207069 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      Photographs and negatives include: Meredith Skura, the Rice University Art Gallery exhibit "SuperThrive," Scottie McDonald, Irie Time, and Stephen Hendee.
    - February 3, 2000, 207070 (Box 12, Folder 5)